Johnny! Come outside.
乔尼  出来
What? Who is it?
什么  谁在外面
It's your father-in-law. I need to talk to you.
是你岳父   我要和你谈谈
What's up?
什么事
Oh, Let me get rid of them. Sorry.
哦  我来帮你弄走他们  抱歉
No problem-o. I was kinda diggin' the attention.
没关系  我还挺喜欢他们围着我转的
Can they stay? I don't think they're ready to leave, yet.
他们能留下来吗  我觉得他们还不想走
Come on. Go to your mother.
走吧  去找你们的妈妈去
-Look, you want to stay here, right? -Of course!
-听着  你想要留下来  对吧  -当然想
This is the first place where I can really be myself. I haven't felt this alive since they invented stuffed-crust pizza.
这是第一个我可以完全做我自己的地方  自从他们发明了芝心披萨以后  我从来没有那么充满活力过
Well, then. We've got some work to do.
好吧  那我们就有事情要做了
Okay, so here's the plan.
听着  我有个计划